[♪ opening theme song playing]
[creaking]
[Genau exhales]
[Stark grunting]
[GENAU] As I thought,
a challenge, indeed.
It's as if we're fighting
multiple master swordsmen
at once.
On top of the sheer number
of attacks,
his reflexes and stamina
far exceed those of any man.
He's overpowering Stark.
If this becomes
a battle of endurance,
-we are sure to lose.
-[Stark grunts]
[GENAU] Should we retreat
and regroup?
No.
He's faster than us.
He would chase us down.
[STARK] This is bad.
Frieren was right.
I can't read his attacks.
Only one option.
[GENAU] That fool...
I told him to deflect
his attacks.
You are mine.
[GENAU]
He took the hit intentionally?
Tough young man.
I am impressed.
You are far sharper
than I supposed.
Be it slight, you created
just the opening I need.
It's over, Revolte.
Of course, I remember you.
How could I ever forget
the partner of the last
first-class mage I slaughtered?
The situation was similar
to this one, no?
You bravely ventured forth
to slay my allies
while your partner defended
the village.
By the time that you returned
from your path of glory,
there was absolutely nothing
you could do for him.
Don't you want to know
how your partner died?
Silence.
I should thank your
fallen colleague for teaching me
a valuable lesson
about mankind.
Fine, then.
I will silence you myself.
In that case,
allow me to grant you
a final piece of advice.
Search the wreckage
more carefully,
you may well find a survivor.
[GENAU] A child?
Enjoy your last breaths.
[Genau grunts softly]
[Genau thuds]
[JUNG] I did it!
Did you see me get him,
Lord Revolte? Praise me!
[REVOLTE] Well done.
You have my thanks.
[GENAU]
My judgment was clouded.
My mind's eye focused
on memories of him.
There couldn't have been
a child.
That much
should've been obvious.
It is just as your partner
illustrated for me.
Humans will protect their young
no matter what it may cost.
[Genau chuckles]
[GENAU] Don't be so certain.
If that were true,
there would be much more light
in the world
than I see today.
I haven't crossed paths
with many fools willing to die
protecting children
they've never met.
I've only known one.
Seems he was a kind boy.
I would wager
that was his undoing.
It's the same in every era.
Kind mages always lead
the shortest lives.
[GENAU]
He met a magnificent end.
♪
[SERIE] So even you can speak
empty words.
Genau, you're an unpleasant man.
You don't possess
a grain of kindness.
Never change that.
As you command.
[REVOLTE] Though killing
brings me no great pleasure...
I shall end your misery.
[Genau scoffs]
To think my final act
was one so horribly
out of character.
[Stark grunting]
[REVOLTE] Gracious.
I have faced many a warrior,
and never have I
encountered a foe
who could withstand
a direct blow
from one of my blades.
You can still move after that?
You would've been better off
playing dead, you fool.
[STARK] Then we would've lost.
[grunts]
And I don't give up so easily!
The winner of any battle
is the last man standing!
Perhaps you're not
the good person
I thought you were.
You're simply an idiot.
Though I suppose
there is some valor in that.
Let us venture into
the jaws of death as one.
The closer that he brings us
to our demise,
the greater the catharsis
we shall feel when we survive.
Somethin' to look forward to.
Now, let's hurry up
and get there.
[FERN] What should I do?
Mistress Frieren disappeared
at some point.
Getting to watch from afar
every once in a while
is a relaxing treat.
[HEMMUNG] Concealing your mana
will not help you hide.
I meticulously crafted this fog
with magic of my own.
It detects
and identifies targets
from the faintest trace
of mana.
Useful,
as no living creature can
conceal their mana completely.
[FERN] Visibility is poor,
and he's blocking my attacks.
He's a bad matchup for me.
[METHODE]
I can sense Miss Fern.
She seems to be
struggling as well.
It's understandable,
her opponent's magic is
unlike any I have faced before.
Medrozobalt.
What's so important over there?
Your only opponent
right now is me.
I'm aware.
[METHODE]
There is nothing unconventional
about this demon's
fighting style.
Her combat is steady
and technique tried-and-true.
She defends while she attacks.
Her fundamentals are solid.
I cannot find
the slightest opening.
I would be remiss to try
and face her head-on.
In an ideal world,
Miss Fern and I would
work together
to bring them both down.
But it's likely this fog has
powerful mana-detection
capabilities.
Unfortunate...
Miss Fern's stealth
is her greatest asset
and she can't use it.
Meaning...
our situation would
greatly improve
if this fog were removed
from the picture.
Time to get a little rough.
♪
[SOLIDE] What's this?
Her attack pattern changed.
I know this fighting style.
I have seen it before.
These tactics are similar
to those used
by a demon hunting clan
who lived on the Plateau.
They dedicated their lives
to massacring my kind.
They were insane.
And it seems you may be, too.
You and I should be
a good match.
Now then, let's fight fair.
[Revolte yells]
[GENAU] Such speed...
I can't land a single spell.
His movements are no longer
masterful and measured.
They're savage
and erratic, like those
of a mindless predator.
[grunts]
[Genau chokes]
[GENAU] Despite the grievous
wounds we dealt,
he fights on undaunted.
His resilience is superhuman,
and his stamina
is seemingly inexhaustible.
If this keeps drawing on,
he'll beat us by attrition.
[Stark grunts]
[Revolte scoffs]
♪
[Revolte grunts]
[Stark grunts]
Genau, his swords!
If they can fracture,
they can shatter!
They have grown brittle.
It appears he's
lost the essential focus
to maintain the mana
his many weapons require.
Just three left!
[SOLIDE] Strange.
What is this dichotomy?
Her attacks
are undoubtedly ferocious,
but I sense no bloodlust
behind them.
[METHODE] My...
You really are astute.
Though I fear the speed
of your notice
leaves a lot to be desired.
I've already finished
analyzing this pesky fog.
When all one knows is warfare,
the only spells they learn
are those for combat.
Were it any other member
of my clan
standing here before you,
you would certainly defeat them,
for they lack
a fundamental insight.
Magic is incredibly fun.
[Methode blows]
[METHODE] Erilfrachte.
[HEMMUNG] They cleared the fog.
How pointless.
I can just as easily
summon it again.
Now where has that girl
run off to?
♪
[SOLIDE]
Hemmung's mana vanished.
♪
[SOLIDE] An attack?
Where'd it come from?
Zoltraak.
[SOLIDE] She's so far!
[Methode chuckles softly]
[FRIEREN] The trajectory
of a long-distance shot
from outside the range
of detection
cannot be predicted.
Impressive. Truly.
[Fern sighs]
I'd really rather not fight
such a difficult fight again.
♪
[Revolte yelling]
[Stark grunting]
Just two more left to go!
[Revolte grunts]
[GENAU] One!
[Revolte yelling]
[Stark yells]
You're disarmed. It's done.
Only humans would see
empty hands as harmless
when they're weapons
just the same.
Your fatal assumption was
to believe me rendered blunted
without the boon of my blades.
Now victory is mine.
[GENAU] Fatal assumption.
I think you'll find
both our species
are capable of those.
You clearly have no idea
how tenacious my kind can be.
[REVOLTE] Huh?
♪
[Revolte gasps]
[STARK] Cleaving Light!
[Revolte grunts]
-[Revolte yells]
-Now, Digardnacht.
[STARK] For what it's worth,
you seem like
a good person to me, too.
You're still trying
to defend the village,
even after it's been destroyed.
I couldn't do that.
♪
There, see?
You're still here
trying to save me.
I knew it.
You're a good guy after all.
[Genau groans]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[straining]
We live to meet again.
I really am incapable
of dying properly, aren't I?
It would seem that way.
[GENAU] Enough, I can move.
[Genau grunts]
How is Stark?
[METHODE] A little worse
for wear maybe.
But he'll live
to fight another day.
When I arrived, I prioritized
healing him over you.
[gasps]
[GENAU] I see.
Are you displeased?
[GENAU] No. He conducted himself
surprisingly well.
If you wish to linger,
Miss Frieren's party
will be staying in the village
while he recovers.
♪
[STARK] Good. I'm practically
back to baseline.
[FRIEREN] He's doing push-ups.
He's a real marvel of nature.
Or perhaps a freak of it.
You're so mean to me.
[METHODE]
Miss Frieren, I couldn't help
but notice your party
is lacking a priest.
Once this request
draws to a close,
I'll have a fair bit
of free time on my hands.
I could accompany you,
should you wish it.
[Fern gasps]
The Northern Plateau
can prove dangerous
without the spells of a priest.
No, we'll be okay.
I can't cast any advanced level
healing magic like you,
but I do know
some lesser priest spells
I could lean on in a pinch.
If we find ourselves
in serious trouble,
we can always run away.
It's worked pretty well so far.
Besides, prudent or not,
I think we'd like to keep our
priest slot open for a while.
You never know
who you might bump into again.
And, well...
For some reason,
Fern seems unhappy
whenever you're around us.
Oh, goodness. Have I somehow
made her hate me?
Well, reciprocated or not,
I still very much
love you, Miss Fern.
And that adorably angry face
of yours.
Methode, the Chivalric Order
of Norm is here.
They're set to depart soon.
And we'll be accompanying them
back south.
Understood.
[GENAU] It would seem
this is where
we must say goodbye.
So, Stark, how are your wounds?
Healed and ready
for the next fight!
I see.
I owe you three a sizable debt.
One I intend to repay.
[METHODE] Mister Genau.
Say it.
Many thanks to you
for all the help.
Yeah, right back at you.
May the both of us
live long lives.
[Genau chuckles]
-[GENAU] Let's go.
-Right.
Take care.
[GENAU] Sure.
Till next we meet.
♪
[STARK] Hey,
was it the right move
to turn that down?
Methode's priest offer.
The sole priest this party
has a place for is Sein.
Yeah, obviously.
But she's a pretty older woman.
Don't you think
Sein'll complain
that we didn't bring her along
with us?
[FRIEREN]
Use your head, Stark.
This party's "older woman"
spot is already filled.
[Stark chuckles]
[STARK] How could I forget?
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[FRIEREN] I suppose it shall
depend on the reward.
[overlapping chatter]
[HEITER]
I'm so bored, I could die.
[SAILOR] I've looked up to him
ever since I was a child.
-[FERN] What does it say?
-[FRIEREN] " Himmel's memoirs."